themetrail.com 2018-06-29

# Privacy – ThemeTrail

ThemeTrail.com (“Website”) collects and manages user data according to the privacy policy (“Policy”) as outlined below. This Policy is part of ThemeTrail’s Terms of Service. By using this Website you represent that you have the legal capacity to enter into a binding agreement, that you agree to the terms of this Policy and the Terms of Service.

### Data Collection

This Website collects anonymous data to monitor traffic and bug fixing, such as the internet protocol address, browser type, the browser language, and timestamps.

In order to access your account, you need to provide us with personal information such as your name and email address. All login based features are using cookies to store information about your session. You can disable or delete those cookies in the privacy settings of your browser, and still use this Website, with the downside that you have to enter your login details every time anew.

You can at any time view, update and remove your account data. If you choose to delete your account, all your data will be deleted, too.

### Cookies

A cookie is a simple text file that contains certain data, sent by a server to a browser; stored by the browser. If you are not happy with this common practice, you should not use this Website.

This Website is using both “session” as well as “permanent” cookies. Session cookies will be deleted when closing the browser. Permanent cookies will are being stored they expired or deleted.

This Website is using Google Analytics remarketing codes to log when users view specific pages or take specific actions on a website. This allows us to provide targeted advertising in the future. If you do not wish to receive this type of advertising from us in the future you can opt out using the [DoubleClick opt-out page](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb#display_optout) or the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).”

### Data Usage

We may use your personal information for:

  * Administrational purpose
  * Enable our Service on this Website
  * Payment processing
  * Ensure communication
  * Prevent fraud and increase security

We will never share your personal information without your permission, unless:

  * Legally required
  * Needed to resolve, prevent or address fraud
  * To protect our Service, legal rights, or that of others

We may contact you by email to share information and offers related to your purchase, or to communicate with you about our Service or this Website, such as a notification about an update of our terms. If you do not want to receive certain emails you can opt out at the bottom of any email or by editing your account preferences.

To improve our Website and Service aggregated, anonymized data is periodically transmitted to external services such as Google Analytics (anonymized data) and MailChimp (email address). To learn more about how these third parties handle your data please study their privacy policies.

To simply opt out of Google Analytics please install the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

To provide dedicated support and make sure you receive the best possible customer experience we may need to share personal information with our internal and external team. These people do not have any right to use any of your personal information beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby agree to this common practice.

We may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the transferred business assets. Moreover, if we, or substantially all of our assets, were acquired, or if we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of us or our assets may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Security

We will do anything in our power to take technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. You acknowledge that the transmission of information over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet. You are responsible for keeping your password and other login details confidential. We will not ask you for your password over emails, only when you login to the Website.

_Last modified: March 17, 2014_
